Two, three!
Action!
Where's Building A?
Over here
Will you come with me?
Cut!
Sorry
Were you nervous?
I'm sorry
I forgot the line
Let's do it again
Okay
Two, three!
Action!
Do you have
something to say?
Huh?
What?
Why isn't he talking?
If you…
Only if you are fine…
Ah, I'm sorry
Cut!
Let's have a lunch break
It's okay
I'm sorry
Gosh, what's wrong
with me?
It's just
"Only if you're okay"
Damn, why can't I do that?
Well
no wonder
he never got attention
after acting as a child
Why would he have been
unknown for so long?
And you know that guy
Shin Yoo-il…
Everyone knows
how he became a star, huh?
Who knows? They
could be the same kind
Shin Yoo-il could be
but Hyesung is not
You'll see
You'll find him better
than you expected
Since when were you
so generous, Director?
I'm not a director
Coffee truck's here
Have a coffee break
[Please support Hwi-rim!
From Shin Yoo-il]
Thank you
Hyesung
-Thank you
Okay
[Please support Hwi-rim!]
[From Shin Yoo-il]